twitterbackgroundsgallery.com 2010-11-20

# Privacy Policy : Twitter Backgrounds Gallery

This website is owned and operated by Webhues Web Productions. We understand you value your privacy. At Webhues Web Productions, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe. This Privacy Policy governs information you provide to us or we learn from your use of this website and tells you how we may collect, use, and in some instances share this information.

### Information Webhues Web Productions Collects and How We Use It

**Information You Provide**

We may ask you to provide us with personal information if you would like to participate in some activities available on, or benefit from services offered on, this website. Personal information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, your name, mailing address, telephone number, email address, personal and professional interests. Through the use of forms we may collect this information to help provide you with Webhues Web Productions services and respond to your requests. We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from other Webhues Web Productions services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services.

In general, the types and amount of personal information collected for these activities will vary depending on the activity. We try to limit our requests for personal information to information we believe is minimally necessary to achieve our stated collection purposes.

We may also use aggregate information collected from our users. This information does not personally identify you and is used to help enhance the website and our services.

In addition, you may voluntarily decide to post, include, and transmit information through publicly accessible forums (i.e., such as user comments and blogs). Please keep in mind that any information that is disclosed in these publicly accessible forums is public. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Usage Tracking**

We track product usage data to improve the services we offer to our users. We collect user traffic patterns throughout our website. This information is collected to help improve website flow and usability. In addition, we track click-through information, including IP addresses, to our website from the reports and emails we sent to our customers. This is done to gauge the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns and to discourage fraudulent use. However, we do not correlate this information with the personal information of individual users.

**Cookies**

We may place a text file called a “cookie” in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain personal information although it will enable us to relate your use of this website to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other websites. Webhues Web Productions may use cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). In addition, Webhues Web Productions may use encrypted cookies to authenticate the user on each page after the user logs onto the website. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you have set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. Some Webhues Web Productions features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

**Our Usage of Personal Information**

We process personal information as described above and also for such purposes as:

  * To deliver our services to users;
  * To highlight featured members on our website or in promotional material;
  * To conduct research and analysis in order to maintain and improve our services;
  * To alert you to service updates, special offers, updated information and other new services. You may opt-out of these communications if you so choose;
  * To contact you in response to requests for information such as “Contact Us.”

**Children**

Consistent with the federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we do not, nor will we, knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requiring parental consent. Any person who provides their personal information to Webhues Web Productions through this website represents that they are 13 years of age or older.

**User Access**

We make a good faith effort to provide you with access to your personal information to correct data that may be inaccurate or delete data at your request. We may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, would be extremely impractical, or where information is required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes.

### Webhues Web Productions Transfer and Information Sharing Policy

We do not share personal information collected on this website with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. We may provide personal information to or permit access to personal information by our vendors and service providers for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf or where such access is incident to their assisting us. Webhues Web Productions does not otherwise share personal information about website users with third parties unless doing so is appropriate to carry out a user’s request or it reasonably believes that doing so is legally required or is in Webhues Web Productions’ interest to protect its property or other legal rights or the rights or property of others.

**Merger, Sale or Reorganization of Webhues Web Productions**

If Webhues Web Productions should ever file for bankruptcy or have its assets sold to or merged with another entity, information Webhues Web Productions receives from you, from this website, is a Webhues Web Productions asset and may be transferred.

**Affiliated Websites, Other Websites, and Advertisements**

This Privacy Policy applies to websites and services that are owned and operated by Webhues Web Productions. We do not exercise control over the websites of third parties that you may link to or view as part of a frame on a page on this website. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data, or solicit personal information from you. We are not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.

**Third Party Advertising**  
May of the ads appearing on our sites were not selected and delivered by us, but by network advertising companies that manage and provide advertising for our sites. Information about your visits to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other PII), is used to serve ads to you.

Third-party ad servers may collect and use Non-PII about your visits to our sites and other sites in order to present advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice or to opt out of having this information used by third-party ad servers to provide targeted ads, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp>.

The companies that provide advertising for our sites and other sites typically gather data about consumers who view their ads. Often, that data is anonymous – linked only to a numbered cookie on a user’s computer. Networks collect and analyze this data to make a variety of inferences about each consumer’s interests and preferences. The result is a profile that attempts to predict the individual consumer’s tastes, needs, and purchasing habits. That profile enables the advertising companies’ computers to make split-second decisions about how to deliver ads directly targeted to the consumer’s specific interests. This is called online preference marketing.

Some of these third parties track and analyze anonymous usage and browsing patterns of our visitors and community members. All data collected by these third parties on behalf of our sites is owned and used by us, but is licensed to the third party for the purposes of creating behavioral information segments. We use this information to help provide our advertisers with more targeted advertising opportunities, which means that users see advertising that is most likely to interest them and advertisers send their messages to people who are most likely to be receptive, improving both the viewer’s experience and the effectiveness of the ads. In addition, the third parties can sell the behavioral information segments to other third parties for use in ads on other sites.

**International Visitors and Customers**

This website is hosted in the United States. If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law please note that you are transferring your personal data to the U.S. which does not have the same data protection laws as the EU and by providing your personal data you consent to:

  * the use of your personal data for the uses identified above in accordance with this Privacy Policy; and
  * the transfer of your personal data to the U.S. as indicated above.

### Security

No data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure security on our systems. We use secure server software (SSL) and firewalls to protect your information from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software.

If Webhues Web Productions learns of a security systems breach we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. By using this website or providing personal information to us you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy and administrative issues relating to your use of this website. Webhues Web Productions may post a notice on our website if a security breach occurs. Webhues Web Productions may also send an email to you at the email address you have provided to us in these circumstances. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us at  
_twitbackgallery [at] gmail.com_

### Changes and Updates

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the “effective date” on the Privacy Policy. For changes to this Privacy Policy that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of personal information you have provided to us, we will attempt to obtain your consent before implementing the change. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed about how we are protecting the Personal Information we collect. Your continued use of this website constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.

### Contacting Webhues Web Productions

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about Webhues Web Productions or this Privacy Policy, please email us at _twitbackgallery [at] gmail_. _com_ In the event that we are still unable to resolve your concerns Webhues Web Productions is committed to cooperating to achieve a proper resolution of your privacy concerns.

Postal Mail Address:

Webhues Web Productions  
1553 Church Street  
San Francisco, CA 94131
